Sunny Lee

SOFTWARE ENGINEER



0466 797 101



sunnbobby@gmail.com



github.com/sundogu



<u>linkedin.com/in/sundogu</u>

EDUCATION

BACHELOR'S DEGREE,

Software Engineering (Honours)
University of Queensland
2016 - Present

INTERNATIONAL BACCALAUREAT DIPLOMA,

Queensland Academy Health Sciences

2011 - 2014

IB 36 (OP4 eqv)

SKILLS

Programming / Development:

- Java
- Python
- C/C++
- JS
- C#
- HTML/CSS
- SQL
- Vue

Industry Knowledge:

- Git
- Linux / Windows
- Agile Methodologies

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Motivated and easily-adaptable Software Engineer with 2 years of experience in software development for various projects and clients. Several group-work opportunity and experiences in an Agile development environment. Fluent in multiple programming languages with preference towards OOP.

EXPERIENCE

Software Developer

DNUI Start-Up - Dalian, China / Jun 2019 - Jul 2019

Android app developer using Java, Kotlin, MySQL and Android Studio. Responsible for UI/UX design, MVC architecture design, feature development, implementation and also documentation.

Software Design

Mind Initiative - St Lucia, Brisbane / Feb 2019 - Jun 2019

Android app / WebApp developer using JavaScript, HTML, CSS. Responsible for developing User Stories, Use Cases, Project Specification in a SCRUM working environment as well as marking up prototypes ranging from low to high fidelities.

Software Engineering Intern

SystemWeb - Taipei, Taiwan / Dec 2018 - Feb 2019

Full-stack web development using JavaScript, Vue, Node.js, WordPress and GraphQL. Responsible for developing a new company website to replace the old site as well as participating in researches towards the new upcoming feature - RoboAdvisor.

Software Developer

HackerSpace - St Lucia, Brisbane / Jul 2018 - Nov 2018

Website developer using Python and Django framework. Responsible for developing a new HackerSpace web portal that centralizes all user accounts related to HackerSpace. Worked in a SCRUM environment in charge of User Stories and features development.